A Guide to the Director's Office Correspondence and Subject Files of the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1954-1986
Library of Virginia
- Series II: History Files, 1956-1986., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 14-31)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Compliments & Complaints, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Compliments & Complaints, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Exhibits, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Exhibits, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Promotions, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Gift Shop, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Mermaid Tavern, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Inquiries, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Inquiries, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Governor's Library Conference, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletter, 1975-1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Job Inquiries, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Performances by Outside Groups, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Band & Chorus, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Invitations & Mailing Lists, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Budget, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Exhibit, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Exhibit, 1974-1976 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Proposed Budget Request, 1974-1976 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Exhibit, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
  - Purchase Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Exhibit, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Material, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1979 Dec. 4 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1979 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1979 Dec. 4 (3 copies) (Box 26)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1979 July 6 (2 copies) (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1979 July 6 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1978 Dec. 2 (3 copies) (Box 26)
  - First General Assembly Proceedings & General Instructions, 1619 (transcription), 1979 (Box 26)
  - Books - Bicentennial Series, 1977-1981 (Box 27)
  - Books - Bicentennial Series, 1975-1981 (Box 27)
  - Books - Revolutionary Road - Scribner Reports & Others, 1977-1983 (Box 27)
  - Books - Revolutionary Road - UVA Reports, 1967-1981 (Box 27)
  - Books - Revolutionary Road - UVA Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
  - Books - Other, 1969-1981 (Box 27)
  - Publications Promotion - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Requests, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Requests for Future Publications, 1977-1979 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Booklet Information, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Medals Inventory, etc., 1977-1981 (Box 27)
  - Book Sales & Contacts - Virginia, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
  - Colleges & Universities - Books, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Public Libraries & High Schools - Virginia, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Medals - Pending Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
  - Inventory List & Addresses, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Medals Purchased, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Silver, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
  - No Medals, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Contact, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Medallion Consignments, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Medals Account Book, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
  - Bicentennial/Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Closeout Actions, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Corporation Finances, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Royalties & Commissions - Bicentennial Items, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Techinarts (Sound System for Bicentennial), 1981 (Box 27)
  - Bicentennial Philatelic Items, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Bicentennial Celebration Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
  - Financial Statements (Monthly) for Bicentennial, 1981 (Box 27)
  - State Agency Expenses for Bicentennial, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Proposals & Contracts for Bicentennial (Support Systems), 1981 (Box 27)
  - Book Binding, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Postcard Folders, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Bermuda National Trust, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Publications - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 27)
  - Tobacco Booklet, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Publications Racks, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Guidebook Printing, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Publications, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Record of Publications - State Library, 1980-1984 (Box 27)
  - Yorktown Victory Center Promotion, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Richmond Independence Bicentennial Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Rochambeau March Reenactment, 1979-1981 (Box 28)
  - Rogers & Clark Documentary Film, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Bicentennial - Debates, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Bicentennial - General, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Attendance Report to the Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Concours, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee - General, 1976-1980 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Victory Celebration - Boy Scout Jamboree, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Book Promotion, 1977-1980 (Box 28)
  - Governor Dalton's Yorktown Victory Center Letters, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Jefferson, Adams, Monroe Project, 1979 (Box 28)
  - King's Mountain, N.C., Celebration, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Special YVC Exhibit Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 28)
  - Virginia Highway Map, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Victory Celebration - Brochures, 1979-1981 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Victory Celebration - Funding, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Victory Celebration - Music, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Victory Celebration - Peninsula Area Municipalities' Involvement, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Naval Review, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Sons of the Revolution - General, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Sons of the Revolution - Valley Forge Project, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Schools & Colleges Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Yorktown Celebration Shipwreck Project, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Commemorative Stamps, 1977-1980 (Box 29)
  - Transfer of Capital from Williamsburg to Richmond, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - VIP Visitations, 1978-1980 (Box 29)
  - Wagon Train Project, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Celebration - Wine Tasting, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center Waterfront Project, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Exhibits, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Inquiries, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Ships, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Trustees Meeting, 1980 May 3 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Special Events, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Exhibits, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Gift Shop, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Restaurant, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Western Virginia Bicentennial Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 29)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Eastern Virginia Bicentennial Committee, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Groups & Conventions, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Requests for Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Promotions, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Gift Shop, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Performances by Outside Groups, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Publications, 1978-1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Mermaid Tavern, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Job Inquiries, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Vehicles, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Ledger - Profit Loss, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission Binder - Certificates of Insurance, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 29)
  - Rochambeau March Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown 1881 Research, 1968-1973 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Concessions, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Special Events, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Recreated Units, 1980-1982 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 29)
  - Gloucester Bicentennial Celebration, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Festival Day Schedule, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission & Reception Drafts, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 May 28 (Box 29)
  - American Frontier Culture Museum Letters, 1982-1983 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Federal Commission, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 May 28 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 July 9 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 May 7 (Box 29)
  - America's Victory Celebration at Yorktown, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Oct. 13 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Revolutionary War Map, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Dept. of Highways & Transportation - Director of Motor Vehicle Service Facilities, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 May 28 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Analysis on Investments, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Executive Committee Minutes, 1981 June 13 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 May 9 (2 copies) (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Apr. 18 (Box 29)
  - Freedoms Shrine Project, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Oct. 13 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Apr. 18 (Box 29)
  - Financial Report, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Contracts, n.d. (Box 29)
  - Battle of the Capes Celebration, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Biennium Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 29)
  - World Turned Upside Down, n.d. (Box 29)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee Budget, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - George Washington Northern Virginia Bicentennial Center - Financial Report, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Oct. 13 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1980 Apr. 18 (2 copies) (Box 29)
  - Donors, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1981 Apr. 18 (multiple copies) (Box 29)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Indexing project, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Indexing project, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Indexing project, 1974-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletters, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletters, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)